crunch.com 2010-12-29

# Crunch - Privacy Policy

  * At Crunch we respect your privacy. We do not share, rent, sell, or otherwise use any personal information you have given us to any third party without your permission, except when required by law, subpoena or other legal process or in order to protect the safety of the public. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. Since this policy may change over time as we modify or expand our services, we suggest that you check from time to time in order to understand how we treat your personal information. Your use of this website and its services constitute your agreement to the terms of our privacy policy. If we decide to change those policies, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what personal information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Your continued use of this website and its services constitute your agreement to any such changes. We will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. We will use this information in order to customize and enhance the services it offers its customers. Examples of such information are: name, age, gender, business, home or postal address, e-mail address, phone numbers, and travel preferences. We may share non-personal aggregate, or summary, information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties, but we do not sell or share any information at the individual customer level.

###### What information do we collect?

Currently, Crunch.com gathers information (such as name, e-mail address and zip code) strictly for contact purposes when users opt to fill out an e-mail submission form to inquire about our company and about membership. In some cases we ask for other optional information including additional contact information and certain demographic information (such as phone number and gender).

###### How do we use your information?

We may use your information to communicate special offers, promotions and information about our company to you via email. If you do not wish to receive these emails you will have the option to opt out of future mailings (see the section below). We may also use your information to compile usage statistics and other data regarding the use of the Web site services. We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties, outside of the limited circumstances referenced in the paragraph immediately below. We may, however, share with partner’s aggregated statistical data that includes users' demographic information but does not identify them. We reserve the right to provide any and all such aggregated and non-individually identifiable data to third parties.

###### How do we use your email information?

At Crunch we respect your concerns about privacy. We collect email information to provide a more personalized and relevant experience. If you give us your email address on the home page, when you inquire about membership or sign up, we will send you emails about exclusive offers, news at Crunch and new club openings. If you have previously opted out of receiving emails from us, providing updated information will act as an 'opt back-in'. If you want to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, simply click on the unsubscribe link located on the bottom of all of our emails. Although we strive to update our email list as frequently as possible, you might receive another contact before we are able to remove you. Please note that you will continue to receive Member Services related communications as it pertains to your member account. Crunch may use any of your contact information held on file (including Email, Mailing, Phone & Fax) to communicate with you in relation to day to day administrative activities, such as freeze requests, online purchases and important service alerts. Crunch never sells or rents your name, e-mail address, or any other personally identifiable information to third-parties.

###### We only share user information in the ways described below:

Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. We will disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties for tracking purposes, to charge your credit card (or process your check or money order, as appropriate), fill your order, improve the functionality of our site, perform statistical and data analyses, deliver your order and deliver promotional emails to you from us, removing repetitive information from customer lists, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. For example, we must release your credit card number to confirm payment; and release your mailing address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

Protection of Crunch LLC. and Crunch: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is necessary to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Crunch LLC., our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

###### Do we use cookies?

We use cookies to enhance your experience on our web site. For example, a cookie enables us to remember the region or specific club page you have visited so the next time you return to our site you do not have to select that club or region again. You can set your Internet browser (like Internet Explorer or Netscape) to warn you every time a cookie is sent, or to turn off all cookies. See your browser's Help menu for these instructions. By disabling your cookies you will not have access to some of the features that enhance your user experience on our site.

###### How do we protect children on our web site?

We are committed to making a safe environment for children on our site. When we collect information for membership inquiry purposes, users are informed they must be at least 18 years of age or have parental consent to provide personally identifying information to us. We encourage parents to monitor children's Internet use to keep them safe while navigating Crunch.com and all other areas of the Internet.

###### Does this Privacy Policy apply to external links found on this Web site?

While this site may contain links to other sites, please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' away from Crunch.com to another Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

###### How can you contact Crunch?

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, other areas of our Web site or our clubs, please contact us. Your feedback is always welcome and appreciated.
